<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theme on 1st Nanpantan Scouts</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/theme/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theme on 1st Nanpantan Scouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/theme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Admissions Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admissions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;1st-nanpantan-scout-group-admissions-policy&#34;&gt;1st Nanpantan Scout Group Admissions Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The aim of 1st Nanpantan Scouts is to provide as many opportunities to as many young people as possible through scouting. To ensure a fair and transparent admissions system, the following has been agreed upon by the Trustees.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-admissions&#34;&gt;General Admissions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Places for older sections will be offered to those who are already part of 1st Nanpantan as a priority over newcomers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wait lists will be open as spaces become available. Wait lists will then be closed when there are sufficient young people on the list (for example, 30 names on the Squirrels waitlist).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Facebook will be used to provide up-to-date information on which lists are or are not open at any one time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If a child is unable to attend any section, they are not able to hold a place by paying until their child is old enough for the next section.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;squirrels&#34;&gt;Squirrels&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waiting List:&lt;/strong&gt; Only those under 4 will be able to put their name into the waiting list. It is recommended to add your child to the waiting list as soon as you can.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offer of a Place:&lt;/strong&gt; The places available depend on how many children are leaving that term to move to Beavers. A place will be offered based on position on the waiting list once a child turns 4. A place at Squirrels will only be offered once. If the place is not taken up or you don’t feel your child is ready, there is the option to move onto the Beavers waiting list. It is not possible for a Squirrels place to be postponed until the child is older.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;beavers&#34;&gt;Beavers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waiting List:&lt;/strong&gt; This waiting list is only for those who were on the Squirrels waiting list. It is not possible to join this list in any other way.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offer of a Place:&lt;/strong&gt; A place will be offered as soon as one becomes available, based on the position on the waiting list once the child turns 6. A place at Beavers will only be offered once. This could be for either a Tuesday or Wednesday evening depending on spaces. If the place is not taken up, the child will be taken off the waiting list system for 1st Nanpantan.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-sections-scoutscubsbeavers&#34;&gt;Other Sections (Scouts/Cubs/Beavers)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If space becomes available in any of these sections, it will be advertised on Facebook, and young people will be taken on a first-come, first-served basis. This is unlikely and should not be relied upon.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;minimum-attendance-policy&#34;&gt;Minimum Attendance Policy&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our group requires each young person to attend a minimum of 50% of the meetings each term, unless extenuating circumstances apply. If this is not met, the place may be offered to another young person.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;volunteer-status&#34;&gt;Volunteer Status&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Adults who undertake a commitment to weekly volunteering as a uniformed leader with 1st Nanpantan scouts will have an opportunity for their child to join as soon as a space becomes available.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;loughborough-scout-groups&#34;&gt;Loughborough Scout Groups&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can find the location of some of the groups &lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/maps/jdauA5GazJGxQYbx5&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
